so here I am in
[Music]
jakata uh 10,000
people say hello hello where the
[Music]
widget here is AR now come here today uh
this is going to
bef's largest audience ever yes and so
all the drinks at the bar he is paying
for tonight he's my boss so if anyone
wants to come for drinks he is paying
tonight so we have audience all the way
over there and all the way over
there AR could you take this and just go
for a walk around the
[Music]
tell
one 2 3
up that's
[Music]
it touchdown
that is scarier than skydiving
[Music]
yeah in New Zealand yeah that's what I'm
talking about that's what I'm talking
about woohoo that was awesome man he I
even sound like that guy yeah the D here
in Jakarta what is this place called AR
PG PG PG sorry is this where uh all the
con do they have concerts here and uh
normally for the Expo Exposition
Exposition exp exp yes yes and I think
this is uh the largest uh indoor like
Stadium or whatever function hall that
will C about 10,000 people
wow I want to be shown also my name is
Ari from Jakarta
I love deal
bye okay see you later
[Music]
okay
it's not what you want it's what you do
with
youi for
[Music]
are